One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Calm Belt
‫الحزام الهادئ‬
Look! It's a huge sea king!
‫!انظروا! إنّه ملك بحر ضخم‬
And it's... fighting something?!
‫هل يقاتل؟‬
It's dead! Something out there killed it!
‫!إنّه ميّت! لقد قُتل‬
Cheer
‫تشجيع‬
But it's huge!
‫لكنّه ضخم - لم أستطع رؤية ما قتله -‬
This sea is scary!
‫يا لخطورة هذا الخليج‬
A guy...?!
‫رجل؟ - !أنت! من أنت؟ -‬
What a pain...
‫...يا إلهي‬
Okay!
‫...مـ‬
Dark King Rayleigh!
‫ملك الظّلام ريلي‬
– What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Oh, it's you guys. We met at Sabaody Archipelago.
‫هذا أنتم. تقابلنا في أرخبيل شابوندي‬
He was the first mate of Roger, the King of the Pirates!
‫كان نائب قبطان ملك القراصنة روجر‬
Well, my ship sunk during a storm, so I had to swim the rest of the way.
‫في الواقع، غرقت سفينتي في العاصفة ولم يكن لديّ خيار سوى أن أسبح‬
A storm?! This is the Calm Belt; these waters are never rough!
‫عاصفة؟ الحزام الهادئ هادئ دائمًا، لا يهيج أبدًا‬
What storm?!
‫لا ينبغي أن تحدث عاصفة‬
Wait...! So your ship wrecked farther away, meaning you swam that entire distance?!
‫ما يعني أنّ سفينته تحطّمت في مكان بعيد وسبح كلّ المسافة إلى هنا؟‬
I have a good breaststroke.
‫أنا أجيد سباحة الصّدر جيّدًا‬
That's not the point!
‫هذا ليس بيت القصيد‬
Then, the one fighting that sea king...
‫...إذًا، كان ملك البحر ذاك‬
– ...was you?!
‫يقاتلك؟‬
Only a legendary pirate could do that!
‫فقط قرصان أسطوريّ يستطيع فعل ذلك‬
Oh, I'm sorry.
‫آسف‬
– What are you sorry for?!
‫لِمَ الأسف؟‬
Oh, right!
‫صحيح‬
I assume Luffy is here on this island.
‫أفترض أنّ لوفي-كن في هذه الجزيرة‬
Did you hear?
‫هل سمعتنّ‬
Center of the Island Isle of Women, Amazon Lily
‫مركز جزيرة إمبراطوريّة النّساء أمازون ليلي‬
The Snake Princess and her entourage just left to deliver food to Luffy!
‫...أنّ أميرة الأفاعي والبقيّة‬
I wanna stretch his body again!
‫أريد تمديد جسده ثانيةً‬
They said they'll invite him over when he gets better.
‫قلن أنّه سيدعينه بعد أن تتحسّن حالته‬
I can't wait!
‫لا أطيق الانتظار‬
I didn't expect to see him again this soon!
‫لم أتوقّع رؤيته ثانيةً مبكّرًا هكذا‬
Yeah, maybe I'll make clothes for him again...
‫...أجل، ربّما سأعدّ له ثيابًا ثانيةً‬
without frills!
‫بلا زخرفة‬
Oh, to be separated from my dearest so soon after our marriage...
‫نحن منعزلان مع أنّنا عروسان‬
I feel like a tragic heroine!
‫أشعر كبطلة مأساة‬
"But Hancock... No, my dear wife!"
‫"لكن يا هانكوك... لا، زوجتي العزيزة"‬
"Y-Yes!"
‫"نـ-نعم"‬
"No matter how far apart we are,
‫"مهما كنّا بعيدين عن بعضنا، حبّنا أبديّ"‬
"Luffy!"
‫"لوفي"‬
Oh, my sweet husband! Right now, my heart is aflame!
‫!يا زوجي الحنون! قلبي مشتعل‬
I keep telling you, Snake Princess,
‫ما قلت من قبل يا أميرة الأفاعي‬
just because someone hugs you and calls you by nyame,
‫فقط لأنّ أحدًا يعانقك أو يناديك باسمك‬
it doesn't mean you are married.
‫لا يعني أنّكما متزوّجان‬
Then, what constitutes marriage?
‫إذًا، ما الّذي يعدّ كزواج؟‬
Ah... There's nyo easy answer to this.
‫لنرَ... ذلك سؤال صعب‬
You can't go to Sabaody with those wounds.
‫لا يمكنك الذّهاب لشابوندي الآن بذلك الجرح‬
But I gotta see my friends right away!
‫لكنّي أريد رؤية أصدقائي في أسرع وقت‬
I promised them I'd be there.
‫يجب أن أذهب إلى هناك كما وعدت‬
But listen...
‫...لكن استمع لي‬
Hm? It looks like...
‫يبدو أن الغواصة ذهَبَت‬
Oh, Luffy!
‫لوفي-كن‬
What?! It's old Rayleigh!
‫ماذا؟ العمّ ريلي‬
Glad I found you so quickly.
‫مسرور لرؤيتك في هذا الوقت القريب‬
What're you doing here?!
‫لِمَ أنت هنا؟‬
I was about to go back to Sabaody using your vivre card.
‫كنت على وشك الذّهاب إلى شابوندي باستخدام الفيفر كارد‬
Is everyone...?
‫هل رأيت أصدقائي؟‬
No, it's unlikely they've made it back yet.
‫لا، لا أظنّ أنّهم وصلوا إلى هناك بعد‬
I gave my vivre card to Shakky...
‫...أعطيت الفيفر كارد خاصّتي لشاكي‬
Otherwise... I couldn't move about freely like this.
‫لكي أذهب حيثما شئت‬
Dark King Rayleigh! Is it really you? I can't believe it!
‫!ملك الظّلام ريلي! أهذا أنت حقًّا؟ لا أصدّق‬
You must be the former Warlord...
‫...لا بدّ أنّك الشّيتشيبوكاي السّابق‬
What's wrong?
‫ما الخطب؟‬
I just... I didn't expect to meet a living legend here.
‫في الواقع، لم أتوقّع رؤية أسطورة حيّة هنا‬
Here. Isn't this hat important to you?
‫خذ. أليست هذه القبّعة مهمّة لك؟‬
It is. Thanks.
‫أجل. شكرًا‬
After all... just doesn't feel right without it!
‫لا أشعر بالارتياح من دونها في النّهاية‬
Did you happen to see a pirate crew here?
‫هل رأيت مجموعة قراصنة هنا؟‬
Trafalgar Law? His ship just left.
‫إن كنت تقصد ترافالغار لاو فقد غادر لتوّه‬
He recommends another two weeks of bed rest.
‫قال أنّ عليك الاستراحة في الفراش لأسبوعين آخرين‬
He saved your life, didn't he?
‫لقد أنقذ حياتك، أليس كذلك؟‬
What a waste! After coming all this way...
‫...يا للخسارة! وصلنا لذلك الحدّ‬
I never got to see the female-only empire...
‫أردت دخول الإمبراطوريّة المحرّمة على الرّجال‬
Bears were allowed in.
‫كنّ يسمحن بدخول الدّببة‬
– Shut up!
‫اخرس‬
I'm sorry.
‫آسف‬
– What a pushover!
‫ضعيف جدًّا‬
I wonder what the Dark King is up to.
‫أتساءل ما الّذي ينوي ملك الظّلام فعله‬
Storms tend to follow in the wake of a D.
‫...مهما كان، أنا واثق أنّ "الدي" سيجلبون عاصفة مجدّدًا‬
I can't wait to see him again...
‫لا أطيق الانتظار لرؤيته ثانيةً‬
Is that Rayleigh?! I cannyot believe my eyes!
‫ريلي؟ لا بدّ أنّك ريلي‬
Oh, Gloriosa! It's been awhile!
‫!غلوريوسا! مضى وقت طويل‬
Rayleigh!
‫ريلي - ري-سان -‬
Oh, you two are here too!
‫أنتما هنا أيضًا‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي‬
– Hey, Big Sis!
‫يا أختي! كيف تتجاهلين الرّجل الّذي أنقذ حياتك؟‬
Then... you know old Rayleigh?
‫تعرفن العمّ ريلي؟‬
We do.
‫أجل - إنّها قصّة طويلة -‬
Luffy, it's good to see you up and about.
‫لوفي، أفقت إذًا الآن‬
I lost sleep from worry.
‫لم أذق طعم النّوم لأيّام من قلقي عليك‬
You must be hungry. I brought some food.
‫لا بدّ أنّك جائع. أحضرت بعض الطّعام‬
So go ahead and dig in...
‫...لذا بادر وكُل‬
You cannyot even look at him.
‫لا تستطيعين حتّى النّظر إليه‬
How can you claim to be married?
‫فكيف تسمّينه زواجًا؟‬
Serve him a–
‫...اخدمه‬
Serve him a meal already!
‫قدّم له وجبةً بسرعة‬
Jinbe! This food is not for you!
‫!جينبي! هذه ليست لك‬
You can only have a little.
‫يمكنك أكل القليل‬
O-Okay. Luffy, why don't we just eat?
‫حـ-حسنًا. لوفي-كن، ما رأيك أن نأكل؟‬
Luffy, you have to eat. To eat is to live!
‫لوفي-كن، عليك أن تأكل. الأكل هو الحياة‬
That's it! That's the Luffy I know!
‫!هكذا! أحسنت يا عزيزي لوفي-كن‬
Thank you for bringing me the letter from Shakky.
‫شكرًا لإحضارك الرّسالة من شاكي‬
Sounds like she has nyot changed.
‫يبدو أنّها لم تتغيّر‬
Yeah, she hasn't changed a bit since you were living in Sabaody.
‫أجل، إنّها على نفس حالها مذ كنت في شابوندي‬
She's doing fine.
‫إنّها بخير‬
These girls of yours have grown quite beautiful and strong over the past thirteen years.
‫أصبحن هؤلاء الفتيات جميلات جدًّا وقويّات في غضون السّنوات الـ13 الماضية‬
Rayleigh, Shakky, and Elder Nyon,
‫ريلي، شاكي، الجدّة نيون‬
the three of you protected us when we were running from the Celestial Dragons.
‫حميتمونا أنتم الثّلاثة عندما كنّا نهرب من التّنّانين السّماويّين‬
But we have a problem.
‫لكن لدينا مشكلة‬
We're supposed to shelter Luffy from the Marines.
‫علينا أن نوفّر الملجأ للوفي من البحريّة‬
It's true that Rayleigh knyows Luffy from before,
‫مع أنّ ريلي يعرف لوفي من قبل‬
but that he was able to guess Luffy's location so easily is indeed troubling.
‫إن كان يسهل توقّع أنّ لوفي هنا فيجدر بنا أن نقلق‬
Huh?! What a familiar face!
‫ماذا؟ يا له من وجه مألوف‬
You wouldn't happen to be Rayleigh, would you?!
‫أنت ريلي، أليس كذلك؟‬
You just nyoticed?! Get your head out of the clouds!
‫هل لاحظت الآن فقط؟ ما مدى فتنك به؟‬
No, I don't think the Marines will be able to guess his whereabouts.
‫كلاّ، لا أظنّ أنّ البحريّة يمكنها أن تتوقّع أنّه هنا‬
To begin with, the one who sent him here...
‫أساسًا، الرّجل الّذي قذفه بعيدًا‬
told me the direction in which to look.
‫أخبرني أنّه أرسله في هذا الاتّجاه‬
I'm an officer in the Revolutionary Army.
‫أعمل لصالح الجيش الثّوريّ‬
We're connected by fate.
‫بما أنّ لديّ صلة بهم‬
I wish to help them escape.
‫أريد أن أدعهم يهربون من هنا‬
Oh? I'm in disbelief.
‫لا أصدّق ذلك‬
So where's our little Monkey now?
‫وأين هو مونكي-تشان الآن؟‬
Beats me...
‫لا أدري‬
Let me apologize for my abrupt manner earlier.
‫أعتذر عن أسلوبي الجافي سابقًا‬
Can I talk to you for a moment?
‫أيمكنني أن أحدّثك للحظة؟‬
I don't have...
‫...لا أملك‬
much time left.
‫الكثير من الوقت‬
Straw Hat should be...
‫...ينبغي بقبّعة القشّ‬
If you follow the direction Bartholomew Kuma launched Luffy,
‫يوجد في الاتّجاه الّذي أرسل بارثولوميو كوما لوفي-كن إليه‬
you find the Isle of Women.
‫جزيرة النّساء‬
When I thought about how Luffy managed to infiltrate the great prison...
‫عندما فكّرت في كيف استطاع لوفي-كن التّسلّل إلى السّجن العظيم‬
it dawned on me that Hancock must've smuggled him aboard a Marine ship.
‫اتّضح لي أنّ لوفي-كن ...تسلّل إلى سفينة بحريّة على الأغلب رفقة هانكوك، لكن‬
Since Hancock hates both the government and men,
‫بما أنّ هانكوك تكره كلاًّ من الحكومة والرّجال‬
it's unlikely she'd board a government ship, especially not to shelter a man.
‫لا أظنّ أنّها ستركب سفينة حكومة‬
This is all just speculation, though.
‫والآن، هذا الجزء نظريّ بالكامل‬
Then how about this?
‫لكن ماذا عن هذا؟‬
Let's suppose Hancock fell in love with our little Monkey.
‫لنفترض أنّ هانكوك وقعت في حبّ مونكي-تشان‬
Then everything makes sense.
‫حينها سيكون كلّ شيء منطقيًّا‬
Our little Monkey is a real stud.
‫مونكي-تشان شخص وسيم‬
And if I were Hancock,
‫وإن كنتُ هانكوك‬
I'd pull one over on the Marines by hiding him on the Isle of Women.
‫كنتُ لأمنحه الملجأ في جزيرة النّساء لأخدع البحريّة‬
The idea seems pretty subjective, Shakky.
‫هذه نظريّة ذاتيّة جدًّا يا شاكي‬
A woman's intuition is a fearsome thing.
‫حدس النّساء مذهل‬
That's my Shakky!
‫هذه شاكي الّتي أعرفها‬
She could nyot be more right! See for yourself.
‫لقد أصابت كبد الحقيقة كما ترى‬
Oh? You like it? Good!
‫حقًّا؟ هل أعجبك؟ جيّد‬
The Marines would never act on such a ridiculous theory.
‫لن تتحرّك البحريّة بناء على نظريّة سخيفة كهذه‬
So this place is safe.
‫لذا هذا المكان آمن‬
Now, let's get down to business.
‫والآن، لندخل صلب الموضوع‬
Luffy.
‫لوفي-كن‬
You said you're gonna head for Sabaody, didn't you?
‫قلت أنّك ذاهب لشابوندي، أليس كذلك؟‬
I gotta get back to my crew.
‫أنا بحاجة لرؤية أصدقائي‬
And you're sure you want to do that?
‫أهذا ما تريد حقًّا؟‬
Sabaody Archipelago...
‫أرخبيل شابوندي‬
Don't you remember what happened there?
‫أتذكر ما حدث لكم في تلك الجزيرة؟‬
Everyone, focus on escaping!
‫ركّزوا على الهرب جميعًا‬
We can't beat these guys! Not now! Not yet!
‫لا يمكننا هزيمة هؤلاء الأشخاص في مستوانا الحاليّ‬
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
‫...لم أستطع أن أنقذ أيّ أحد من أصدقائي‬
Do you think you can face those tremendous powers as you are now?
‫هل تظنّ أنّك تستطيع مواجهة تلك القوى الجبّارة في مستواك الحاليّ؟‬
But... I...
‫لكنّي... أنا‬
Do you want to be reunited with your friends just to endure the same fate?
‫هل تريد أن تجتمع مع أصدقائك فقط لتواجه نفس المصير؟‬
I have a suggestion.
‫لديّ اقتراح لك‬
Of course, whether you follow it...
‫وبالطّبع أنت حر في قبوله أم لا‬
Meanwhile, on the Bowin Archipelago in the Grand Line... Bowin Archipelago Grand Line
‫في نفس الأثناء في أرخبيل بوين في الغراند لاين‬ ‫أرخبيل بوين بالغراند لاين‬
Stop! Usopp'n!
‫!توقّف! أوسوبّن‬
Don't stop me, Heracles'n!
‫لا توقفني يا هراكلسن‬
Usopp is...
‫...أوسوبّ‬
moving his body, which has grown immensely...
‫يحرّك جسده الّذي صار ضخمًا‬
from eating the forest's abundant variety of food...
‫...من أكله لطعام وفير ومتنوّع في الغابة‬
and is running.
‫ويركض‬
It's impossible'n!
‫هذا مُستحيلُن‬
No, it's not! I just have to keep trying!
‫!لا، ليس كذلك! لهذا سأحاول ثانيةً‬
I can do it this time!
‫يمكنني النّجاح هذه المرّة‬
There you are!
‫وجدتك‬
Get out of my way!
‫ابتعدي عن طريقي‬
Lethal...
‫النجم‬ ‫هيساتسو‬
Yikes'n! Usopp'n!
‫!لان! أوسوبّن‬
Are you okay'n, Usopp'n?
‫هل أنت بخير يا أوسوبّن؟‬
Damn...
‫...سحقًا‬
You're too reckless'n.
‫،لا يمكنك فعل ذلك إن حاولت الخروج من هذه الجزيرة‬
terrifying creatures will halt your progress...
‫ستعترض طريقك أشياء حيّة مرعبة‬
and push you back into the forest'n!
‫وتعيدك إلى الغابتِن‬
Nothing will stop you from entering the island'n...
‫لن يوقفك أيّ شيء من دخول الجزيرَتِن‬
but once you've set foot on it, you're dead!
‫لكن فور أن تطأ عليها فأنت ميّت‬
No one leaves this island alive'n!
‫لا أحد يغادر هذه الجزيرة حيَّن‬
And my name is...
‫واسمي هراكلسن‬
What?! Usopp'n! Where'd you go?!
‫!ماذا؟! أوسوبّ! إلى أين ذهبت؟‬
Oh! Danger's afoot'n!
‫إنّه في خطرِن‬
A great sea beast has come to the island'n!
‫لقد دخل المخلوق البحريّ الجزيرة توًّا‬
Usopp'n is in danger!
‫أوسوبّن في خطر‬
The sweet scent wafting from the Bowin Archipelago...
‫...رائحة أرخبيل بوين الحلوة تجذب انتباه‬
draws in giant insects and massive birds...
‫...الحشرات العملاقة والطّيور العملاقة‬
A sea hippo!
‫إنّه فرس نهر بحريّ‬
No time to stand here gawking at it...!
‫لا ينبغي أن أفتن به الآن‬
The scents lure them deeper into the island,
‫...تغويها الرّائحة أعمق إلى الغابة‬
where they find that the forest is filled with food.
‫حيث تجد الغابة المليئة بالطّعام‬
Entering the island is one thing...
‫...من السّهل دخول الجزيرة‬
but leaving proves difficult!
‫...لكن من الصّعب مغادرتها‬
Outta my way!
‫ابتعدي عن طريقي‬
Lethal Exploding Star!
‫النجم المتفجر الفتاك‬ ‫هيساتسو كايكو بوشي‬
I'm getting off this island!
‫سأخرج من هنا‬
Stop getting in my way!
‫لا تعترضي طريقي‬
Usopp'n!
‫أوسوبّن‬
The island is about to move again!
‫ستتحرك الجزر ثانيةً‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
Usopp'n! Hang onto a tree!
‫!أوسوبّن! تشبّث بشجرة‬
This again?!
‫هل يحدث هذا ثانيةً؟‬
It's preparing to feed!
‫ستأكل شيئًا‬
This flower that's disguised as an island is called...
‫...اسم هذه الزّهرة الّتي تبدو كجزيرة‬
the Bowin Archipelago, a carnivorous plant also known by its scientific name, the stomach baron!
‫هو ما يدعوه النّاس بأرخبيل بوين‬
Usopp'n!
‫أوسوبّن‬
What's the matter with you, Usopp'n?!
‫ما خطبك يا أوسوبّن؟‬
Ever since that news coo brought the paper, your whole demeanor has changed!
‫تغيّر حالك مذ قرأت الصّحيفة الّتي أحضرها نورس الأخبار‬
I...
‫...أنا‬
I don't have a single moment to waste here!
‫لا أملك وقتًا أضيّعه هنا الآن‬
Luffy lost his brother in the war...!
‫فقد لوفي أخاه في الحرب‬
I'm sure he's going through hell right now!
‫!لا بدّ أنّه يواجه وقتًا عصيبًا الآن‬
When your friend is having a hard time...
‫عندما يواجه صديقك وقتًا عصيبًا‬
you should be there for him!
‫عليك أن تكون إلى جانبه‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي‬
Birdie Kingdom
‫مملكة تورينو‬
You go now, little tanuki? We just become friends!
‫هل ستغادر الآن فعلاً أيّها التّانوكي؟ صرنا أصدقاء لتوّنا‬
I am. I read in the newspaper that my friend is in trouble,
‫نعم، قرأت في الصّحيفة عن محنة صديقي‬
so I need to hurry and get back.
‫لذلك أريد العودة في أقرب وقت ممكن‬
I met Luffy's brother in Alabasta.
‫...لا أصدّق ما حدث لأخ لوفي‬
How could such a terrible thing happen?
‫الّذي التقينا به في أرباستا‬
I need to hurry back to Luffy and treat his wounds.
‫أريد رؤية لوفي قريبًا وتقديم الرّعاية الطّبّيّة له‬
He can't help but act recklessly.
‫لا بدّ أنّه ضغط كثيرًا على نفسه كالعادة‬
Little tanuki...
‫أيّها التّانوكي‬
I'm glad you were able to make peace with the birds.
‫أنا سعيد لأنّكم على وفاق مع الطّيور‬
It all thanks to little tanuki risking life to persuade birds!
‫هذا لأنّك خاطرت بحياتك وتحدّثت معها‬
Well, y'know...
‫...كلاّ‬
You guys, try to be nice to the humans, okay?!
‫اسمعوا يا رفاق، عيشوا مع البشر بسلام‬
The humans only need the plants that grow on the tree.
‫كلّ ما يريدونه هي الأعشاب المختلفة الّتي تنمو على تلك الشّجرة‬
He right!
‫!هذا صحيح! لا نريد بيضك ولا نريد أذيّتك‬
We not same as people who force you from homeland!
‫نحن مختلفون عن أولئك الّذين طردوك من جزيرتك الأمّ‬
I have to say, the medicine harvested from the plants on this tree work very quickly.
‫بما أنّك ذكرت الأمر الآن، الدّواء الّذي صنعتموه من النّباتات الّتي على تلك الشّجرة مفيد للغاية‬
My wounds are about healed.
‫شفيت جراحي سلفًا‬
Yeah! They very special recipes from ancestors.
‫بالطّبع! هذا دواء توارثناه أبًا عن جدّ‬
If I had to choose, I'd prefer to stay on this island and research its flora.
‫بصراحة، أريد البقاء في هذه الجزيرة ودراسة النّباتات‬
I'm sure I've never come across their components before.
‫أنا واثق أنّ هنالك مكوّنات غير مألوفة لي لكنّني لا أملك الوقت‬
Come other time!
‫تعال وزرنا ثانية‬
He right! We give little tanuki big welcome!
‫!هذا صحيح! أنت مرحّب بك دائمًا أيّها التّانوكي‬
Really? You'd do that for me?
‫فعلاً؟ سرّني سماع ذلك‬
After I reunite with my friends, I'll definitely tell them about this place!
‫عندما ألتقي بأصدقائي، سأخبرهم عن هذه البلاد‬
And then I'll come see you all again!
‫وسآتي لزيارتكم ثانية‬
Here. You get hungry on long trip.
‫خذ هذه. أمامك رحلة طويلة وستجوع‬
Thanks.
‫شكرًا لك‬
Come again, little tanuki!
‫زرنا ثانية أيّها التّانوكي‬
It's cotton candy!
‫إنّها حلوى قطنيّة‬
Okay, everyone! Try and get along!
‫حسنًا يا رفاق، كونوا لطفاء مع بعضكم‬
– Bye-bye, little tanuki!
‫الوداع أيّها التّانوكي‬
All right, I've got my lunch and my cotton candy.
‫حسنًا، لديّ علبة طعام وبعض الحلوى القطنيّة‬
I'm all set to meet back up with Luffy and the rest!
‫سأنطلق نحو نقطة اللّقاء الآن‬
I don't have a pirate ship!
‫لا أملك سفينة قراصنة‬
Ah! See you!
‫أجل، إلى اللّقاء‬
Whoa, we're flying so high and fast!
‫نحن مرتفعون وسريعون‬
I'll catch up to the others in no time!
‫سأصل إلى هناك في غضون لحظات‬
Hey, news coo! Can I have a newspaper?
‫!يا نيوز كو! أعطني صحيفة‬
I'll just read while I enjoy my meal.
‫سأقرؤها وأنا أتناول غدائي‬
All the details of the war should be coming to light now.
‫لا بدّ من وجود جديد عن أخبار الحرب الآن‬
Why?! What's going on here?!
‫!لماذا؟! ما الّذي يحدث؟‬
What made Luffy do this...?!
‫ما الّذي دفع لوفي ليقوم بهذا...؟‬
This is Gloom Island on the Grand Line:
‫هذه جزيرة كورايغانا في الغراند لاين‬
Gloom Island
‫جزيرة كورايغانا‬
the remnants of the Muggy Kingdom.
‫أطلال مملكة شيكّيارو‬
An old castle stands resolute against this decrepit land.
‫...حيث توجد بقايا قلعة قديمة من المملكة الّتي هلكت منذ مدّة‬
But a few years ago, a certain man took up residence there.
‫والّتي صارت مأهولة منذ بضع سنوات الآن‬
How could Master Moria die in the war?!
‫لا أصدّق أنّ موريا-ساما مات في الحرب‬
This is torture for my ears. Take your wailing outside.
‫إنّك تزعجين أذنيّ. اذهبي لمكان آخر للبكاء‬
How coldhearted of you! Is that any way to talk to a person in mourning?!
‫يا لقسوتك وأنت تقول ذلك وهناك من هو محطّم بالكامل أمامك‬
Is it too much to offer a few kind words and to bring me a cup of hot cocoa?
‫قل شيئًا لطيفًا وأحضر لي كوب شكولاطة ساخنة‬
Don't forget, I'm your guest!
‫أنا ضيفتك‬
An uninvited guest.
‫لم أدعوك أبدًا‬
You're squatters who took advantage of my absence.
‫أنتما من وطأ هذه الأرض بغير حق أثناء غيابي‬
Regardless...
‫...وأيضًا‬
this article lacks credibility.
‫هذا المقال ليس موثوقًا‬
What?! Then Master Moria possibly survived the war?! Are you for real?!
‫ماذا؟ إذًا، هذا يعني بأن موت موريا-ساما في الحرب مجرد كذبة؟‬
I am not certain whether he still lives...
‫لا أدري إن كان ميتًا أم حيًّا‬
but if memory serves,
‫...لكنّ ما أذكره على الأقلّ‬
Moria was still alive when I last saw him on the battlefield.
‫هو أنّ موريا كان حيًّا في ساحة المعركة‬
But if he didn't die in battle, why run such an article?!
‫إن لم يكن ميتًا، فلماذا قالوا أنّه مات؟‬
Oni...
‫قاطع الغول‬ ‫أوني غيري‬
Saliva won't heal that!
‫كفّ عن وضع بصاق عليه أين تعلّمت هذا العلاج الشّعبيّ؟‬
Damn these guys... How long till they stop showing me up?!
‫قرود لعينة، إنّها تسخر منّي بالفعل‬
I'll never make it to the sea at this rate!
‫لن أصل للبحر أبدًا على هذه الوتيرة‬
Hawk Eye...
‫..."عين الصّقر"‬
You departed the castle some time ago,
‫مرّ وقت طويل مذ غادرتَ القلعة‬
and yet you remain, Roronoa?
‫وابتعدت لهذه المسافة فحسب يا رورونوا؟‬
It seems the rowboat I lent you has been rendered useless.
‫يبدو أنّ القارب الّذي أعطيتك إيّاه صار بلا فائدة الآن‬
Put a sock in it!
‫اخرس‬
I can use it like a piece of driftwood if I swim while holding onto it!
‫سأستعمل الألواح وأسبح مستندًا عليها فحسب‬
This loyalty to your crew is touching, but do not underestimate these beasts.
‫من الجيّد أنّ تهتمّ لأمر صديقك لهذه الدّرجة، لكنّها قويّة‬
Known as humandrills, they are cunning baboons who develop by imitating humans.
‫إنّها تُدعى هيوماندريل‬
Humandrills?
‫هيوماندريل؟‬
Were they to dwell among peaceful humans, they, too, would be peaceful.
‫لكانت قردة مُحِبّة لو أنّها كبرت قرب بشر مسالمين‬
But this land...
‫...لكن على هذه الجزيرة‬
was ravaged by a brutal war seven years ago.
‫كانت هنالك حرب حتّى سبع سنوات مضت‬
When I made this island my home, the scent of blood and smoke yet lingered.
‫عندما أتيت للعيش هنا، كانت رائحة الدّماء والدّخان ما زالت تعمّ المكان‬
The sea of corpses made it nigh impossible to walk.
‫وكانت الجثث متناثرة على الأرض‬
To make my point, these beasts spent their formative years watching ferocious humans.
‫وقد كبرت قردة الرّبّاح هذه وهي تشاهد أولئك البشر العنيفين‬
Their proficiency with human weaponry...
‫وتعلّمت كيف تستعمل الأسلحة وصارت محاربة الغابة‬
Mankind rules over the animals with weapons and intelligence.
‫بإمكان البشر التّفوّق على الحيوانات باستعمال الأسلحة والحكمة‬
But an animal with a weapon is frighteningly strong.
‫لكن عندما تستعمل الحيوانات الأسلحة، تصير أقوى‬
Fitting opponents, perhaps, for a cocksure youth.
‫إنّها تشكّل خصومًا ممتازة لشابّ يافع متغطرس‬
You mean me?!
‫أتقصدني بكلامك؟‬
Who else would I mean?
‫لا يوجد سواك هنا‬
It's dreadfully late. Come to my castle.
‫أوشكت الشّمس أن تغرب. عد لقلعتي‬
The beasts dare not venture near my abode.
‫لن تزعجك هناك‬
I don't take orders from you!
‫لا تملِ عليّ الأوامر‬
I'm going out to sea, right now!
‫عليّ أن أبحر‬
So be it.
‫فهمت. افعل ما يحلو لك‬
I don't give a damn about any warriors of the forest...
‫لا أهتمّ إن كانت محاربة الغابة أو ما شابه‬
I can't spend another moment around here!
‫لا وقت لديّ لأضيّعه‬
Meanwhile...
‫في تلك الأثناء، على جزيرة السّماء الصّغيرة ويذاريا‬
Let me out of here! I'll return everything I stole!
‫!أخرجوني! سأعيد لكم ما أخذته‬
Mr. Haredas!
‫!صحيح! هارداس-سان... استدعوا هارداس-سان‬
Will you please?!
‫أرجوكم‬
We won't let you out! There's no telling what you'll do!
‫لن نخرجك أبدًا، لا ندري ما الّذي قد تفعلينه تاليًا‬
How should we punish this young girl?!
‫كيف نعاقب هذه الآنسة؟‬
Do we flood her cage or strike it with lightning?
‫حُكم بالفيضان أم البرق؟‬
Damn cat burglar!
‫إنّها قطّة لصّة‬
I won't do anything...
‫لن أفعل أيّ شيء‬
Just let me out already!
‫أخرجوني من هنا فحسب‬
No way!
‫مستحيل‬
Hey, hey! Hey, hey!
‫مهلاً، مهلاً، مهلاً، مهلاً‬
Oh, Mr. Haredas!
‫إنّه السّيّد هارداس‬
Hey!
‫مهلاً! مهلاً، مهلاً يا آنسة‬
Okay, stop that.
‫ذلك كثير‬
I heard you were running amok again.
‫يبدو أنّك في حالة غضب ثانية‬
Ta-da!
‫حسنًا‬
But here I have just the thing! Now, take a look!
‫سيساعد هذا. دعيني أريك‬
Tied tightly here are "wind knots"!
‫هذه عُقد هواء مربوطة بشدّة‬
– Mr. Haredas!
‫سيّد هارداس‬
I'm in a real hurry here, so either give me a hand or get my fist!
‫قلتُ "أخرجوني،" أتريد لكمة أخرى؟ أنا في عجلة من أمري‬
– Mr. Haredas!
‫!سيّد هارداس! أيمكنك سماعنا يا سيّد هارداس؟‬
Hey... Haredas... here...
‫...نعم، هذا هارداس‬
A surprise attack! She's a demon!
‫!لقد ضربته بدل الحديث معه !إنّها شيطانة حقيقيّة‬
The doctor! Someone call the doctor!
‫!طبيب! اتّصلوا بالطّبيب‬
She did what?
‫ماذا؟‬
She stole weather balls from the weather patch, and she took our research notes?
‫سرقَت كرات طقس من حقل الطّقس وملاحظات بحوثنا؟‬
It is as you see, Mr. Haredas.
‫كما ترى هنا يا سيّد هارداس‬
Young lady...
‫...يا آنسة‬
I used to be a thief, and now I'm a pirate.
‫كنتُ لصّة في الماضي وأنا قرصانة الآن‬
What's wrong with stealing?
‫فما العيب في السّرقة؟‬
– She's pure evil!
‫!إنّها الأسوأ! أسوأ إنسانة على الإطلاق‬
– We have a true villainess in our country!
‫ثمّة شرّيرة حقيقيّة في بلادنا‬
Like I said...
‫سبق وقلت... أريد الخروج من هذه البلاد‬
I'm begging you, just let me go already!
‫!أخرجوني بسرعة! أتوسّل إليكم‬
I have to hurry! I gave back everything I stole, didn't I?
‫عليّ الذّهاب الآن! استعدتم ما سرقته، صحيح؟‬
Come on, let me out!
‫لذلك أخرجوني‬
Stay back! She's a sinister one, all right!
‫!لا تقتربوا كثيرًا! إنّها عنيفة‬
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
‫ما الّذي حلّ بك فجأة؟‬
I heard you tried to steal a balloon to go down to the surface.
‫حاولت اختطاف منطاد والنّزول للبحر، صحيح؟‬
Amateurs can't use those. You could have died!
‫،لا يستطيع الهواة قيادة منطاد كان من الممكن أن تموتي‬
Look at the newspaper.
‫الخبر في الصّحيفة‬
The newspaper?
‫الصّحيفة؟‬
There's coverage on a man named Luffy...
‫لوفي المذكور في الصّحيفة هو قبطان سفينتنا‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
Oh? This kid?
‫ماذا؟ إنّه هذا الفتى‬
He's the one who wreaked so much havoc in the war that just happened.
‫ذكروا أنّه تسبّب بالكثير من الفوضى في الحرب السّابقة‬
The infamous straw-hat rookie.
‫إنّه ناشئ يرتدي قبّعة قشّ‬
While his crew was scattered across the world...
‫بعد أن انفصل طاقمنا‬
Luffy was left to fight a difficult battle all on his own.
‫لا بدّ أنّ لوفي كان يقاتل في معركة صعبة بمفرده‬
In order to save Ace, he rushed headlong into that Summit War...
‫...وقد شارك في حرب القمّة لإنقاذ إيس‬
but Ace died right before his eyes!
‫ورآه يُقتل أمام عينيه‬
And I was just...
‫ولم أكن... أعلم بالأمر حتّى‬
Luffy will definitely go to our rendezvous point.
‫أعلم أنّ لوفي سيكون هناك في المكان الّذي تواعدنا أن نلتقي فيه‬
Before he's completely broken...
‫قبل أن يُحطَّم بالكامل‬
I need to go and be there for him!
‫أريد رؤيته ودعمه‬
Hurry and let her out!
‫أخرجوها في الحال‬
We locked up a young girl and made her cry!
‫اختطفنا آنسة شابّة وأبكيناها‬
How could we be so cruel?!
‫!يا لعنفنا‬
Mr. Haredas! The key!
‫أعطوا المفتاح للسّيّد هارداس‬
Right, the key!
‫المفتاح، المفتاح‬
There. Now come on out.
‫...حسنًا، بإمكانك الخروج. أنا آسف يا آنسة‬
Where did she go?
‫أين ذهبت الآنسة؟‬
Mr. Haredas is gone too.
‫لا أجد السّيّد هارداس أيضًا‬
– What?! How'd she get over there?!
‫!ماذا؟! كيف وصلت إلى هناك؟‬
Thanks!
‫!شكرًا! مع السّلامة‬
– Huh?! What the...?!
‫!ماذا؟! ما الّذي...؟‬
She faked her tears and took Mr. Haredas hostage!
‫تظاهرت بالبكاء وأخذت السّيّد هارداس رهينة‬
And she has the stolen goods again!
‫وأخذت الأغراض المسروقة أيضًا‬
Weatheria's weather science needs to remain hidden from the world!
‫يجب الحفاظ على علوم طقس ويذاريا سرًّا‬
After her!
‫طاردوها‬
Anywhere will do! Just please, take me down to the surface!
‫!لا أهتمّ إلى أيّ مكان! أنزلني للبحر رجاءً‬
Not possible...
‫...هذا غير ممكن‬
Make it possible!
‫اجعله ممكنًا‬
Luffy... You're safe, right?
‫!لوفي! أعلم أنّك بخير‬
I'm sorry! You were always the one to support us!
‫!آسفة! لطالما دعمتنا أنت‬
Now that you need us, it's our turn to...!
‫هذه فرصتنا لردّ الجميل‬
After her! Don't let her get away!
‫!أمسكوها! لا تدعوها تهرب‬
Oh? Young lady, you don't have to keep up the crying act.
‫مهلاً يا آنسة، لم تكفّي عن التّظاهر بالبكاء‬
Stow it!
‫اخرس‬
Meanwhile, in the land where the genius Vegapunk was born...
‫في تلك الأثناء في جزيرة الشّتاء أرض المستقبل بالديمور‬
Baldimore, a winter island country known as Futureland...
‫...حيث وُلد العبقريّ فيغابانك‬
Intruder alert!
‫هنالك متسلّل‬
Doctor Vegapunk's lab has been breached! It's an intruder!
‫ثمّة من اقتحم مختبر الدّكتور فيغابانك‬
Do not discharge firearms in the lab!
‫لا تستعملوا أيّ أسلحة ناريّة في الدّاخل‬
Treat every single object in there like a world treasure!
‫!تذكّروا أنّكم محاطون بالكنوز النّفيسة! مفهوم؟‬
Roger that!
‫عُلم‬
Halt!
‫توقّف‬
Dammit! The Marines are here too?
‫!تبًّا! لم أتوقّع وجود جنود بحريّة‬
Nope, that'd be bad.
‫كلاّ، لا يجب عليّ ذلك‬
Can't shoot in here!
‫لن أطلق النّار‬
Treasure? That laboratory?
‫كنز؟ ذلك المختبر؟‬
Indeed.
‫نعم، يعمل فيغابانك الآن قائدًا لعلماء البحريّة‬
He is the pride of our country.
‫وهو فخر بلادنا‬
One could even consider his brain as one of mankind's greatest assets.
‫أعني أنّه يمكن وصف دماغه بأنّه ملك للجميع‬
This is where Vegapunk spent the days of his youth.
‫هنا قضى فيغابانك صباه‬
Take a look at that mountain.
‫انظر لذلك الجبل. شكله غريب، صحيح؟‬
Yeah, now that you mention it, what is that thing?
‫أنت محقّ بعد أن نبّهتني إليه... لماذا؟‬
He built that in his childhood,
‫إنّه شيء صنعه عندما كان طفلاً‬
thinking about the citizens who must endure this intense cold.
‫لمساعدة النّاس في هذه البلاد أثناء البرد القارس‬
He modified the forest animals so they would assist in this arduous labor of love,
‫لقد حوّل الحيوانات الّتي في الغابة لقوّة عاملة وكان يكمله‬
but it remains incomplete.
‫لكنّه ما زال غير مكتمل‬
Something to warm the entire island: a ground-heating system.
‫إنّه نظام تسخين أرضيّ سيدفّئ الجزيرة بأكملها‬
However...
‫لكن كما هو الحال في العديد من أفكاره‬
The ideas in his head never saw the light of day.
‫لم يكن قادرًا على تحقيق ما كان في ذهنه‬
He lacked the resources and funding to make them a reality.
‫لم تكن التّكنولوجيا متطوّرة كفاية ولم يمتلك المال أيضًا لتحقيق ذلك‬
Just the sight of him crying when he was unable to help us...
‫لكنّ رؤيته حزينًا لأنّه لم يستطع إسعاد الجميع‬
was enough to warm our hearts.
‫بعثت الدّفئ في قلوبنا‬
That's a super tearjerker of a story!
‫يبعث هذا على البكاء بشكل خارق‬
You think so?
‫فعلاً؟‬
We are all anxiously awaiting the day he comes home.
‫إنّنا في انتظار عودته دائمًا‬
Now that you know, I ask that you never return to that laboratory, what with its...
‫إن كنت قد فهمت فأنا أرجوك ألاّ تتسلّل للمختبر‬
self-destruct button.
‫الّذي يحمل زرّ التّدمير الذّاتيّ‬
The hell...?!
‫ماذا؟‬
That's the worst switch anyone could install, and you just casually mention it?!
‫هل ذكرت توًّا اسم أكثر الأزرار غير المرغوب فيها في العالم؟‬
I didn't know about that switch...
‫لم أكن أعرف ذلك‬
Hey, old guy, let's just go home and have some warm tea!
‫اسمع أيّها العمّ، لنعد للمنزل لنعد ونشرب الشّاي السّاخن‬
No can do!
‫لا يمكنني ذلك‬
The ice-breaker ship is my only way off this island,
‫لأنّ ذلك هو المكان الوحيد الّذي سأجد فيه كاسحة جليد‬
and it's in that laboratory, right?
‫وهي ما أحتاج لمغادرة هذه الجزيرة‬
I have things I need to do.
‫عليّ القيام بذلك‬
You see, I just read in the news that my captain's not doing so hot.
‫عرفت توًّا بأخبار مِحن قبطاني‬
See ya!
‫!مع السّلامة! شكرًا على كلّ شيء‬
Wait! Whatever you do, do not push the self destruct button!
‫!انتظر! إيّاك أن تضغط على زرّ التّدمير الذّاتيّ‬
Like I would, you codger!
‫!لماذا قد أفعل أيّها المغفّل؟‬
Why'd he install that anyway?!
‫لماذا وضع زرًّا كهذا من الأساس؟‬
Hot damn, this is super impressive.
‫كلّ هذا مذهل بشكل خارق‬
These are all just inventions he thought up as a kid?
‫لا أصدّق أنّها مخطّطات من أيّام صباه‬
A lot of these ideas are a couple hundred years ahead of their time.
‫العديد من هذه الأفكار ستحتاج لبضع مئات السّنوات لتتحقّق بالكامل‬
They're right. As an engineer, I would hate it if anything happened to this place.
‫كانوا محقّين، لا أريد العبث بأيّ شيء هنا بصفتي مهندسًا‬
Hey, did you hear? Apparently, there's an intruder in the lab!
‫مهلاً، هنالك من تسلّل إلى المختبر‬
No way! That's terrible news!
‫فعلاً؟ هذا سيّئ‬
Word is, each and every blueprint in there is a priceless treasure.
‫حتّى تصاميم ذلك المكان ستكون قيّمة‬
Take precautions, men! If anything in the genius Vegapunk's lab gets damaged,
‫إن كسرتم شيئًا ما في منزل العبقريّ ...فيغابانك أثناء مطاردتكم‬
it is a severe criminal offense!
‫فسيكون خرقًا للقانون الجنائيّ‬
– Yes, sir!
‫حاضر‬
Oh, a pirate mark!
‫إنّها علامة قراصنة‬
Lemme ask just one thing.
‫أيمكنني أن أسألك عن شيء؟‬
If, by some freak chance, I were to press that switch...
‫...إن ضغطت على ذلك الزّرّ بالصّدفة‬
Old guy?
‫أيّها العمّ؟‬
Would it be my fault?
‫هل ستكون غلطتي أنا؟‬
– Obviously!
‫بالطّبع‬
This incident in Futureland is forever referred to as:
‫...هذه الحادثة في أرض المستقبل، ستُعرف في أرجاء العالم ب‬
"The Nightmare of Baldimore."
‫"كابوس بالديمور"‬
Thank you so much, Dark Lord Satan!
‫شكرًا جزيلاً لك يا ملك الشّياطين ساتان-ساما‬
I never thought I'd see the day when these guys were finally captured and behind bars!
‫لم أحلم أبدًا أن نتمكّن من وضعهم في أقفاص ذات يوم‬
I can't explain it, but when you played that song you composed for us...
‫لا أدري ما السّبب، لكن عندما ...سمعت المقطوعة الّتي ألّفتَها‬
...courage and fighting spirit welled up inside us!
‫ملأت الشّجاعة والقوّة قلبي‬
For the first time in our lives, we stood our ground!
‫وحملتُ الأسلحة وقاتلت لأوّل مرّة في حياتي‬
Of course, we lost anyway,
‫وبطبيعة الحال، انتهى الأمر بفشلنا وقمت أنت بهزيمتهم أخيرًا‬
But thanks to your actions, our kidnapped villagers are safe once more.
‫لكنّ من اختُطفوا عادوا بسلام بفضلك‬
Oh, you! Don't thank me, I only helped a little.
‫إطلاقًا، ساعدتُ قليلاً فحسب‬
Neither gods nor devils are spurred to action by inaction.
‫لن تساعد الآلهة أو الشّياطين أيّ أحد يأبى أن يقاتل بنفسه‬
These are dark times.
‫بما أنّنا نعيش في أوقات كهذه ...أردت أن أحرص‬
to ensure you carry the will to stand against future misdeeds.
‫أنّ بإمكانكم الوقوف بأنفسكم في وجه الشّرّ دوني‬
How benevolent!
‫!يا لرحمته! أظنّ أنّ بإمكاننا التّغيّر من الآن فصاعدًا‬
Thank you very much, Lord Satan!
‫شكرًا جزيلاً لك يا ساتان-ساما‬
And with that, my debt is settled.
‫أعتقد أنّني أدّيت واجبي ناحيتهم‬
At any rate, I could barely believe that news article.
‫والآن... لا أصدّق تلك الأخبار‬
I hope you are well, Luffy.
‫.لوفي-سان، آمل أنّك بخير إنّها أخبار تحطّم القلب‬
Though... I do not have a heart.
‫...رغم أنّ لا قلب لي‬
Luffy, let us sing together!
‫لوفي-سان، لنغنّ أغنية معًا‬
Without further ado, let me soothe your heart!
‫سأذهب إلى هناك لإنقاذ قلبك الآن‬
Dammit! They had an actual devil as a bodyguard!
‫!سُحقًا! لا أصدّق أنّ لهم شيطانًا كحارس شخصيّ‬
If only we had gotten these single-elbowed freak shows back to our homeland,
‫لو استطعنا إحضار هؤلاء البشر ذوي المفصل الواحد في أذرعهم لموطننا‬
we could have made a killing with them on display!
‫لاستطعنا جني ثروة عن طريق عرضهم على المتفرّجين‬
Now, then...
‫...حسنًا‬
If we put these two-elbowed, long-armed freak shows on display,
‫يملك سكّان قبيلة طويلي الأذرع مفصلين في أذرعهم‬
we could make a killing off of that!
‫بإمكاننا جني ثروة بعرضهم على متفرّجين‬
P-Please wait just a minute.
‫مـ-مهلاً لحظة‬
If you do that, you will be no better than them!
‫لا يمكنكم ذلك، ستكونون بذلك تعاملونهم بنفس طريقة معاملتهم لكم‬
What?! Let them go?! If we do that, they'll just–
‫ماذا؟ ندعهم يذهبون؟ سيهاجموننا ثانية هكذا‬
It will be okay. They, too, have made a deal with the devil!
‫لا تقلق، وقّعت عقد شيطان معهم‬
Heed my words, you three.
‫اسمعوا أنتم الثّلاثة‬
For if you break your contract with me by troubling this nation once more,
‫إن خلفتم بوعدكم معي واقترفتم عملاً خاطئًا في حقّ هذه البلاد ثانية‬
eat your hearts!
‫فسآكل قلوبكم‬
We are humbled by your mercy!
‫شكرًا لسماحك لنا بالذّهاب‬
We'll return home immediately!
‫سنعود لموطننا في الحال‬
We'll never come near this country again!
‫لن نأتي لهذه البلاد ثانية‬
– And up we go!
‫حسنًا‬
Huh? What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Why?! What do you think you're doing?!
‫ماذا؟ ما الّذي يحدث هنا؟‬
– And off we go!
‫هيّا بنا‬
Devils aren't real, you bonehead!
‫إنّنا لا نؤمن بالشّياطين أيها الغبي‬
You're pretty strong, but you're helpless once we tie you up!
‫أنت قويّ، لكن لست قويًّا كثيرًا وأنت مربوط‬
When we bring back this rare, moving skeleton...
‫...إن عدنا ومعنا هيكل عظميّ متكلّم‬
...we'll be trillionaires!
‫فسنتمكّن من جني ثروة‬
Wait a second! I have somewhere I really need to get back to!
‫!تمهّلوا لحظة! عليّ الذّهاب لمكان ما‬
Lord Satan!
‫ساتان-ساما‬
This is a disaster! They abducted our Lord Satan!
‫!مصيبة! اختُطف ساتان-ساما‬
prepare to summon a new devil!
‫أيّها النّاس، استعدّوا لاستدعاء شيطان آخر‬
That's right! We're still able to summon devils with our underwear!
‫هذا صحيح، بإمكاننا استدعاء شياطين بملابسنا الدّاخليّة‬
Luffy. We should sing together when things are tough.
‫لوفي-سان، ينبغي لنا الغناء معًا عند المصاعب‬
As a musician, I live for those moments.
‫...ذلك هو دور الموسيقيّين! لذلك انتظرني، سوف‬
Luffy...
‫...لوفي-سان‬
Before that...
‫قبل ذلك‬
Help me!
‫النّجدة‬